本:你在这.我最爱的人.我的英雄.
Ben: There you are.My favourite person.My hero.My pal.My role model.
我的老伙计.我的行为榜样.你有时间吗?
Do you have a second?
克莉丝:没有.这是我最爱的卡通.
Chrissy: No.This is my favourite cartoon.
本:不.我在和迈克说话.
Ben: No.I was talking to Mike.
迈克:没有.这也是我最爱的卡通.
Mike: No, it's my favourite cartoon too.
本:迈克,听着,我.
Ben: Mike listen, I.
克莉丝:嗨!
Chrissy: Hey!
本:听着.我要你今晚开车送我和一个姑娘约会,
Ben: Listen.I need you to drive me on a date tonight with a girl,
这个姑娘很可能成为你的弟媳.
who quite possibly could be your sister in law.
迈克:行了,本.让妈妈或者爸爸开车送你去.
Mike: Come on Ben.Get mum or dad to drive you.
本:那样会毁掉一切的.那个小妞才15岁.
Ben: That would ruin everything.This babe is fifteen years old.
迈克:哦,15岁.一个成熟的女人.不错,本.
Mike: Oh, fifteen.A ripe woman.Good one Bennie.
克莉丝:什么是成熟女人?
Chrissy: What's a ripe woman?
迈克:那样,克莉丝,这很难用文字表达.
Mike: well Chrissy, it's kind of hard to put into words.
克莉丝:开萝尔成熟了吗?
Chrissy: Is Carol ripe?
本和迈克:哈哈.
Ben and Mike: Ha ha.
克莉丝:好像你们这些小子如此亢奋!
Chrissy: Like you guys are so hot!
本:帮帮忙,迈克.求你了,
Ben: Please Mike.Please will you drive me?
你开车送我吗?这个女孩跟我之前见过的女孩不同.她真的喜欢我.
This girl is like no other girl I have ever met.She actually likes me.
迈克:那样我要去看看.行了,本.我开车送你.
Mike: Well this I s have go to see.Alright Bennie.I'll drive you.
本:真棒.而且我还需要你……
Ben: Great.And I also need you to ffaafafafaf.
迈克:什么呀?
Mike: What was that?
本:我需要你为翠西的大学毕业在家的哥哥找个女朋友.
Ben: I need you to find a date for Trish's brother who is home from college.
迈克:喔喔喔.你要我为那个疯姑娘的哥哥找个女朋友?
Mike: Wo wo wo.You expect me to find a date for this crazy girl's brother?
本:我只是向你要一个女人.你有几百个呢.
Ben: I'm just asking you for one woman.You've got hundreds of them.
迈克:没有了.目前我只盯着一个.凯特.
Mike: Not anymore.Just lately I've been seeing one.Kate.
本:哦.她有点高,但是还行.
Ben: Oh.She's a little tall, but ok.
迈克:不,本.他不能拥有凯特.我们的关系非常特殊.
Mike: No Bennie.He can't have Kate.We have a very special relationship.
本:我给你洗一个月的车.
Ben: I'll wash your car for a month.
迈克:那包括里面吗?不,那一定错了.
Mike: Does that include white walls?No, that would be wrong.
本:我都绝望了.这么短的时间我上哪去找一个大学生那样的年纪的女孩子?
Ben: I am desperate.
Where am I going to find a college aged girl who is available at such
short notice?
开萝尔:本,我只是开车接你和这个女孩子.
Carol: Ben, I'm just driving you and this girl.
为什么我必须见她的父母?
Why do I have to meet her parents?
本:为什么?这样他们就明白你是个多么安全的驾驶员.
Ben: Why?So they can see what a safe driver you are.
开萝尔:那不对.
Carol: That isn't true.
本:哦,顺便说一下.
Ben: Oh and by the way.
如果翠西的哥哥问你,你说你五点之前你还是金发女郎.
If Trish's brother asks you, you were blonde until five o'clock today.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:不然我怎么让他和你出去呢?
Ben: How else could I get him to go out with you?
开萝尔:我不会跟任何人约会.
Carol: I am not going on any dates.
本:本.我比你高大.我可以杀了你.
Ben: Carol.I am bigger than you.I could kill you.
翠西:嗨,本杰明.
Trish: Hi Benjamin.
本:嗨,翠西.你答应了.
Ben: hi Trish.You're going.
翠西:你这么担心什么呢?她不算差.
Trish: What were you so worried about?She's not so bad.
开萝尔:不算差!
Carol: Not so bad!
布拉德:嗨.我是布拉德.
Brad: Hi.I'm Brad.
开萝尔:很明显,我弟弟已经告诉你,
Carol: Apparently my brother has given you the impression that you and
你和我将……上耶鲁大学.
I are going.....Yale!
布拉德:啊哈.
Brad: Uh hu.
开萝尔:我们去玩吧.
Carol: Let's party.
翠西:那太棒了,本.那不棒吗?
Trish: That was great Benjamin.Wasn't that great?
本:哦,我喜欢你穿那裙子,颠倒着.
Ben: Oh I loved being upside down with you in that skirt.
布拉德:你觉得这个怎么样,开萝尔?开萝尔!
Brad: How did you like it Carol?Carol!
开萝尔:男孩,那有趣.下一个呢?
Carol: Boy that was fun.What's next?
布拉德:跳伞.
Brad: Parachute drop.
本:这怎么样,翠西?尝试自由落体的感觉?
Ben: How about it Trisha?Up for a little free falling?
翠西:哦,你真讨厌.
Trish: Oh, you are so nasty.
开萝尔:恩,我想我还是在这里坐会儿.
Carol: Um, I think I'm just going to sit this one out.
布拉德:那么,恩,我也坐会.
Brad: Well um, heck so will I.
开萝尔:好的.你知道许多人觉得恶心.
Carol: Ok.You know a lot of people get nauseous.
布拉德:你还要吐吗?
Brad: Are you going to up chuck again?
开萝尔:不,不.而且对不起,
Carol: No, no.And I'm sorry about your shoes.
弄脏了你的鞋.听着,其实我并不喜欢狂欢.
Look, I'm not really a Carnival kind of girl.
在博物馆,剧院,
I mean I feel more comfortable in museums and theatres and libraries.
图书馆,我觉得更加舒适.如果你是萨士比亚迷,
If you are a Shakespeare nut, I'm your girl.
我是你的女朋友.随便说句台词,我会告诉你出自哪一段的.
Quote any line and I'll tell you which play it's from.
布拉德:哦,上帝,这是埃里卡.穿红色套装.那嘴唇,那手指.
Brad: Holy moley, it's Erica.In the red uniform.Those lips, those fingers.
开萝尔:谁?
Carol: Who?
布拉德:知道第二长号手吗?我曾经和她约会.
Brad: See the second trombone?I used to date her.We were practically engaged.
我们其实已经订婚了.讲述不快乐的经历,
Talk about bad timing hu?
啊?我见到了像你一样好姑娘,
I meet a great girl like you and my old fiancé marches back into my life.
而我的未婚妻回到我的生活里.再见.
See you.
开萝尔:再见.我学习了五年的钢琴.
Carol: See you.I took five years of piano lessons.
本:翠西,我发誓这是个以外.
Ben: Trish, I swear it was an accident.Come on.
行了.难道你没有听说过引力?
Haven't you ever heard of gravitational pull?
翠西:我哥哥呢?
Trish: Where's my brother?
开萝尔:本,我回家了.
Carol: Ben, I'm going home.
翠西:哦,他甩了你.
Trish: Oh he dumped you.
开萝尔:对于你说的,他没有甩我.我甩了他.
Carol: For your information, he didn't dump me.I dumped him.Ok.
好了.我回家了,本.
I'm going home Ben.
本:开萝尔,请你了.求他带你回去.如果你有必要的话就打碎他的眼镜.
Ben: Carol, please.Beg him to take you back.Break his glasses if you have to.
开萝尔:你听我说过了,狂欢结束了.
Carol: You heard me, the Carnival is over.
本:我会为你找另外一个约会对象的.嗨,那里有没有孤独的男孩呀?
Ben: I'll find you another date.Hey, are there any lonely guys out there?
开萝尔:我们回家.
Carol: We are going home.
本:开萝尔,请再给我两个小时?
Ben: Carol, please give me two more hours?
可怜弟弟吧,他可从来没有做伤害你的事情.
Have pity on a brother who has never done any harm.Yet.
翠西:哦,本,你真讨厌.
Trish: Oo Ben, you are nasty and mean.
开萝尔:好,我再给你一个小时,不会再多一分钟.
Carol: Alright, I'll give you an hour but not a minute more.
本:两小时.好极了.
Ben: Two hours.Perfect.
开萝尔:本!九点整.整整一个小时,在大转轮那里.
Carol: Ben!Nine o'clock.One hour exactly, by the Ferris wheel.
本:午夜,我知道了!
Ben: Midnight, got it.
开萝尔:准确的说是九点.
Carol: Nine o clock exactly.
本:知道了.凌晨一点.
Ben: Got it.One am.
开萝尔:(在想)本,如果到时你不到这里的话.我数到三,然后走.一,二……
Carol: (in her mind) Ben, if you are not here by the time I count
to three I'm leaving.One, two
杰克:嗨,美人!
Jake: Hey beautiful!Hey you darlin!
嗨,你亲爱的!
You've been warming up that bench for forty five minutes.
你都已经给长椅加热了四十五分钟.想不想过来转一圈?
Are you going for a ride or not?
开萝尔:把我的生命置于只有一个螺钉结构的脆弱转轮的危险!不,谢谢.
Carol: Risk my life on a flimsy wheel with single bolt construction!No thanks.
杰克:哦,没有一点冒险的生活叫什么?
Jake: Oh, what's life without a little risk taking?
开萝尔:哦,上帝.我倒鼓励他了.
Carol: Oh god.I've encouraged him.
杰克:什么?
Jake: What?
开萝尔:如果你一定想知道,我在等我的弟弟.
Carol: If you must know, I'm waiting for my little brother.
解渴:那么从那上面,亲爱的,你可以看到每个人.
Jake: Well from up there darlin, you can see everybody.
开萝尔:不,谢谢!
Carol: No thanks.
杰克:那么你弟弟长的什么样?
Jake: So what does your brother look like?
开萝尔:没人去坐你的转轮.
Carol: There is no one running your ride.
杰克:哦,让它旋转,亲爱的.我看到一个苦恼的女人.
Jake: Oh let it spin darlin.I see a woman in distress.
开萝尔:我告诉你.如果你不再叫我"亲爱的",我就转一圈.
Carol: I'll tell you what.If you stop calling me darlin, I'll go for a ride.
杰克:没问题……小甜心.
Jake: No problem...sweetheart.
开萝尔:(在想)好的,这小黄鼠狼在哪?你甚至连他的味也闻不到.
Carol: (in her head) Ok, where is that little weasel?
哦,不.是布拉德,
You can't even smell him from up here.Oh no.It's Brad.Yale, it figures.
耶鲁大学.他不能看到我一个人坐在这上面.现在怎么办?
He can't see me alone on this thing.Now what?
杰克:别担心,亲爱的.转轮卡住了.
Jake: Don't worry darlin.Wheel is jammed.
开萝尔:那么就弄开.
Carol: Well unjam it.
杰森:我不敢动一个螺栓的结构.
Jake: I dare not with single bolt construction.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
杰克:开玩笑.只要坐稳了.
Jake: Kidding.Just sit tight.Which carte are you in?Everybody stay calm...
你在什么位置呀?各位保持冷静……没有什么好担心的.
Nothing to worry about.
开萝尔:让我离开这死亡陷阱.
Carol: Get me off this death trap.
杰森:我们让它转了,亲爱的.哦,啊!
Jake: We got it going now darlin.Ohh ahh!
开萝尔:你还好吧?
Carol: Are you alright?
杰克:我的脚踝.妈的,受伤了.哦,
Jake: It's my ankle.Damn that hurts.Oh ah.There's my trailer.Ooh, ooh.
啊.那是我的活动房.哦,哦.我的床在那.
The beds over there.
开萝尔:那床.对不起.我还不习惯搀扶男人.
Carol: The bed.I'm sorry; I'm just not used to carrying men around.
伤的重吗?你想要点冰块敷在上面吗,……先生?
Does it hurt bad?Do you need some ice on it Mr...?
杰克:杰克.杰克 蓝岛.
Jake: Jake.Jake Landau.
开萝尔:嗨.我是朱蒂 琼斯.
Carol: Hi.I'm Judy Jones.
杰克:见到你真高兴,朱蒂.哦,这是威廉 萨士比亚作品全集.
Jake: Nice to meet you Judy.Oh, the complete works of William Shakespeare.
杰克:是的,实在的,
Jake: Yeah, verily sweet Juliet.
亲爱的朱蒂.我喜欢在晚上孤独时光读它.
I like to read it in the lonely hours of the night.
开萝尔:哇.
Carol: Wow.
杰克:你惊讶?
Jake: Are you surprised?
开萝尔:不.不,只是我没想到你……
Carol: No.No, it's just that I didn't think that you...
杰克:能阅读?
Jake: Could read?
开萝尔:不.不,不.我是说萨士比亚.
Carol: No.No, no.I mean Shakespeare.
杰克:生活不过是移动的影子.一个贫穷的演员……
Jake: Life's but a walking shadow.A poor play that...
开萝尔和杰克:在舞台上时而高视阔步,时而骄躁不安,
Carol and Man: struts and frets its hour upon the stage and then is heard
然后销声匿迹.这是个痴人说梦的故事.
no more.It is a tale told no more by an idiot.
开萝尔:本!
Carol: Ben!
杰克:什么?
Jake: What?
开萝尔:我得走了.
Carol: I have to go.
杰克:逗留一会.我没有多少机会谈论萨士比亚.
Jake: Stick around.I don't get much chance to talk Shakespeare.
开萝尔:我不能.对不起.
Carol: I can't.I'm sorry.I have to go ruin my brothers bed time.
我得去破坏我弟弟的睡觉时间.很高兴见到你.
It was nice meeting you.
杰克:嗨,朱蒂,等等!等等!
Jake: Hey Judy, wait up!Wait up!
小丑:嗨!杰克.
Clown: Hey Jake.
杰克:嗨,宾克.
Jake: Hey Bink.
杰克:我看到你找了个活的.跟她玩的开心吗?
Clown: I see you found a live one.Show her a good time yet?
杰克:我在努力.
Jake: I'm working at it.
小丑:他得到所有小妞.他们嘲笑我.我不明白.
Clown: He gets all the babes.Me they laugh at.I don't get it.
开萝尔:本!本!本!好呀,他不在这里.
Carol: Ben!Ben!Ben!Great, he's not here.
杰克:很好.那孩子不在这里,不幸运呀?
Jake: Good.The kid's not here.No luck hu?
开萝尔:不.那家伙肯定是太开心了,把时间给忘了.
Carol: No.The kids probably having so much fun he lost track of time.
杰克:玩的开心没有什么错.
Jake: There's nothing wrong with having fun.
开萝尔:我没说不对.
Carol: I didn't say there was.
只是我的开心的概念跟别人有点不同.
It's just that my idea of fun is a little bit different.
杰克:你尝试过风车吗?
Jake: Have you tried the whip?
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: Excuse me?
杰克:风车!
Jake: The whip.
开萝尔:哦,你是说那个转的.我不是那种风车类型的女孩.
Carol: Oh, you mean the ride.I'm not really the whip kind of girl.
杰克:给我五分钟.我每晚都在看他们,
Jake: Give me five minutes.I watch them from up there every night.
现在是终场演奏.
Here comes the grand finale.
开萝尔:我想我然后就得回家了.
Carol: I guess I have to be getting home then.
杰克:为什么?
Jake: Why?
开萝尔:那是因为狂欢将要结束.
Carol: Well cos the Carnival is going to be over.
杰克:也许.
Jake: Maybe.
开萝尔:每个人都将回去.
Carol: Everyone is going to be going home.
杰克:我不了解你,但是我等不到他们离开.
Jake: I don't know about you, but I can't wait for them to leave.
开萝尔:你在说什么呢?
Carol: What are you talking about?
杰克:当他们全走了,这就是我们的乐园.
Jake: When they're gone, it will be our Carnival.
开萝尔:我从来没有自己的乐园.
Carol: I've never had my own Carnival before.
杰克:那时你会有的.我最喜欢乐园的那个时候.没人在这,但是如果你仔细听,你仍然可以听到笑声.
Jake: Then you are due.This is when I like the Carnival best.There is no one here, but if you listen real close, you can still hear the laughter.
开萝尔:你从来不必回家.你每晚都待在这?
Carol: You never have to go home.You get to stay here every night.
杰克:是的.那么什么是你的乐趣?
Jake: Yep.So what is your pleasure?
开萝尔:那,我还没试过垂直降落呢?如果你想体验一下自由下落?
Carol: Well, we haven't tried the parachute drop yet.
哦!本!我忘记了我的弟弟.
If you are in for a little freefalling.Oh!Ben!I forgot about my brother.
杰克:朱蒂,放松点.他可能找另外的途径回家了.
Jake: Judy relax.He probably found another way to get home.
开萝尔:哦,我不是担心他.
Carol: Well I'm not worried about him.
只是我从来没有忘记他的存在.多么美妙的感觉.
It's just that I never forgot that he existed before.What a wonderful feeling.
杰克:那么你不担心他?
Jake: So you are not worried about him?
开萝尔:不担心.
Carol: No.
杰克:让我看看我最爱的地方,在那一切皆有可能.
Jake: Let me show you my favourite place, where anything is possible.
开萝尔:哦,我想去这里.
Carol: Oh, I want to go here.
杰克:但是这只是拍照的.我说的是魔术.
Jake: But this is just photographs.I'm talking magic.
开萝尔:我认为这是我的乐园.哦,这太好了.
Carol: I thought this was my Carnival.Oh, this is great.
杰克:你真的不应该碰那些衣服.
Jake: You really shouldn't touch those costumes.
开萝尔:这是我的乐园.我碰我所想碰的.碰,碰,
Carol: It's my carnival.I'll touch what I want to touch.
碰,碰.那么,你想穿哪件衣服?
Touch touch, touch, touch.So, what costume do you want to wear?
杰克:嗯?
Jake: Uh?
开萝尔:你想要成为什么?
Carol: What do you want to be?
Jake: I don't know.What do you want 矢o be?
杰克:我不知道.你想要成为什么?
开萝尔:我想要成为什么呢?那,
Carol: What would I like to be?
我想做个令人赏心悦目,有魅力,
Well I would like to be a woman who's considered desirable and attractive
风趣的女人.但是不能放弃我的智慧,
and fun.But without giving up my intelligence, or drive, or dignity.
能力和尊严.而且我需要有足够的自信,
And I would love to have enough self confidence so that it wouldn't be
这样来自耶鲁的那家伙就不会甩了我,而是我甩了他.
some guy from Yale dumping me, but me dumping him.
杰克:我想这些衣服都被清洗过了.
Jake: I think that costume is being cleaned.
开萝尔:好,然后.脱衣舞表演者怎么样?
Carol: Ok then.How about a stripper?You don't have to dress up.
你用不着打扮.和我一起照一张.哈哈哈……
Just be in the picture with me.Ha ha ha.
杰克:你是个危险的女人,朱蒂 琼斯.危险女人.
Jake: You are a dangerous woman Judy Jones.Dangerous woman.
开萝尔:那么,你接下来想干什么?
Carol: So, what do you want to do next?
杰克:你怎么想的?
Jake: What do you think?
开萝尔:恩.
Carol: Hmmm.
杰克:恩.
Jake: Hmmm.
麦琪:开萝尔?
Maggie: Carol?
杰森:本,起来.
Jason: Ben, wake up.
本:什么呀?
Ben: What?
麦琪:开萝尔在哪?
Maggie: Where is carol?
本:她不在她房间?
Ben: Isn't she in her room?
杰森:不在.但是她开的车在车道上.解释一下?
Jason: No.But the car she drove is in the driveway.Explain that?
本:啊,我不能.晚安.
Ben: Uh, I can't.Goodnight.
麦琪:本,对我们说实话.
Maggie: Ben, level with us.
开萝尔是不是一起跟你从游乐园回来的?
Did carol come home from the carnival with you, or not?
本:没有.
Ben: No.
杰森:那么你怎么回来的?
Jason: Well how did you get home?
麦琪:你开的车?又一次?
Maggie: You drove?Again?
本:没有.我吸取了教训.翠西开的.
Ben: No.I learned my lesson.Trish drove.
杰森:我想她只有15岁.
Jason: I thought she was fifteen.
麦琪:她怎么会有执照?
Maggie: How did she get a license?
本:我没有说她有执照.我也没有说她吸取了教训.
Ben: I didn't say she had a license.Nor did I say she learned her lesson.
杰克:闭上眼睛.闭上他们.
Jake: Keep your eyes shut.Keep them shut.
开萝尔:好,好.
Carol: Ok, ok.
杰克:快点.快点.准备好了吗?
Jake: Come on.Come on.Ready?
开萝尔:好了.
Carol: Yes.
杰克:就是这个地方.睁开眼睛.
Jake: This is the place.Open your eyes.
开萝尔:娱乐宫.
Carol: A fun house.
杰克:你没有想到吧.来吧.
Jake: You have no idea.Come on.
开萝尔:杰克,杰克!
Carol: Jake!Jake!
杰克:这里,亲爱的.
Jake: Over here darlin.
开萝尔:别这样单独留下我.
Carol: Don't leave me alone like that.
杰克:这里.在这里没有什么可以吓到你的.
Jake: Over here.There's nothing in here that is going to frighten you.
开萝尔:现在这是我所见到的自己.
Carol: Now this is how I see myself.
杰森:你是我所知道的最苗条的胖女人.
Jake: You are the skinniest fat woman I know.
开萝尔:那这是我以前的样子.
Carol: Well this is how I used to look.
杰克:我不相信.这是你今天的样子.
Jake: I don't believe it.This is how you look today.
开萝尔:那么这是我所希望的我的样子.
Carol: Well this is how I wish I looked.
杰克:这是你的样子.
Jake: This is how you look.
开萝尔:不.这是因为镜子和光线.
Carol: No.It's the mirror and the lights.
杰克:不,不是的.我在镜子里看起来怎么样?
Jake: No it isn't.How do I look in the mirror?
开萝尔:很棒.
Carol: Terrific.
杰克:我外貌上看怎么样?
Jake: How do I look in person?
开萝尔:很棒.
Carol: Terrific.
杰克:这告诉你什么?
Jake: What does that tell you?
开萝尔:我喜欢你的样子.
Carol: I like the way you look.
杰克:你让我震惊.
Jake: You take my breath away.
开萝尔:在这是不是太热了点?我是说,也许我们该…… (接吻)
Carol: Is it getting a little warm in here?I mean maybe we should...(kiss)
杰克:你知道我们可以更舒服的,我说,在我的活动屋.
Jake: You know we could be so much more comfortable, say, in my trailer.
开萝尔:活动屋!
Carol: Trailer!
杰克:别有歪主意.我也很高兴待在这里.
Jake: Don't get the wrong idea.I'd be happy to stay here too.
开萝尔:歪主意.我们去你的活动屋.这与我想像的一点不同.
Carol: The wrong idea.Let's go to your trailer.This isn't anything like I thought it would be.
杰克:什么不同?
Jake: What isn't?
开萝尔:活动房.书.你.
Carol: The trailer.The books.You.I wouldn't change a thing.Particularly you.
我不想改变一样东西.尤其是你.太完美了.
It's perfect.
杰克:什么是完美的?
Jake: What's perfect?
开萝尔:今晚.你使我觉得很漂亮.
Carol: This night.You make me feel so beautiful.
杰克:我们今晚在这要做的,朱蒂,是……
Jake: What we are going to do here tonight Judy is...
开萝尔:杰克.我不想让谎言成为今晚的一部分.我的名字不是朱蒂.
Carol: Jake.I don't want a lie to be any part of this night.My name isn't Judy.
杰克:什么?
Jake: What?
杰克:很高兴见到你.
Jake: Well it's nice to meet you.
开萝尔:还有我19岁,我住在家里.不是因为我不得不这样,而是因为我想我需要这样.
Carol: And I'm nineteen years old and I live at home.Not because I have to but because I think I want to.
杰克:很好.
Jake: It's ok.
开萝尔:还有我在哥伦比亚法学院上学,
Carol: And I got o school at Columbia Pre Law,
但是我不能真正确定其他的了.
but I'm not really sure anymore.
杰克:我不需要知道这些所有的一切.
Jake: I don't need to know all this.
开萝尔:我需要你知道这一切.我需要你了解我.
Carol: I need for you to know all this.I need you to know me.
杰克:我了解你很多了.
Jake: I know you plenty.
开萝尔:我没有真正约会过,因为我从来没有想过男人会对我感兴趣.
Carol: I never really dated too much because I never really thought that
知道你展示了我.
men were interested in me.Until you showed me.
杰克:听着,开萝尔,朱蒂,无论你叫什么?我不在乎.
Jake: Look carol, Judy, whatever your name is.I don't care.
开萝尔:你现在没有必要告诉我关于你的任何方面.因为我相信你.
Carol: You don't have to tell me anything about you.Because I trust you.
杰克:闭嘴!
Jake: Shut up!
开萝尔:我说什么了?
Carol: What did I say?
杰克:瞧,很晚了.为什么你不回家呢?
Jake: Look, its getting late.Why don't you go home or something?
开萝尔:听着,很抱歉,如果我说的什么让你不高兴.晚安.
Carol: Look I'm sorry if I said something to upset you.Goodnight.
杰克:别哭了,亲爱的.
Jake: Stop your crying darlin.
开萝尔:对我来说没有事情有好的结果.什么也没有了.
Carol: Nothing ever works out for me.Nothing!
杰克:你全想错了.
Jake: You got it all wrong.
你不知道今晚你自己有多棒.
You don't know how well it worked out for you tonight.
开萝尔:你在开玩笑?一个我曾经不认识的家伙,
Carol: Are you kidding?A guy I don't even know, from Yale.Dumps me.
来自耶鲁大学.甩了我.
And another guy, that I am ready to do...
而另一个家伙,我正想对他……一些重要的事情,
some important stuff with, kicks me out of his trailer.
把我逐出他的活动屋.那么很明显我有些方面不对.
There is obviously something wrong with me.
杰克:你有些方面不对!你在干什么?
Jake: Something wrong with you!What are you doing?
还在照哈哈镜?
Looking in one of those funny mirrors again?
开萝尔:我说得全都是事实.我一点也没有吸引力.
Carol: I'm just seeing things the way they are.I'm not attractive to be with.
杰克:你把一切都搞混了.你很漂亮,
Jake: You got it all mixed up.You are beautiful Carol.
开萝尔.你不能等着像我这样的人说你那些话,因为你根本不知道他们是谁,
You can't go around waiting to hear it from guys like me,
或者他们想干什么.他们会伤害你.
because you don't know who they are or what they want.They could hurt you.
开萝尔:你不是那种人.
Carol: You are not like that.
杰克:哦,我……曾经是.
Jake: Oh I...used to be.
开萝尔:你说的是当你说我漂亮的时候?
Carol: Did you mean it when you said I was beautiful?
杰克:你没听见?别来问我.
Jake: Don't you listen?Don't ask me.
对你自己说,"
Say to yourself "I'm beautiful and any guy who doesn't want me is a damn
我很漂亮,哪个男人不要我他就是大傻瓜".
fool".
开萝尔:我不能说那样的话.
Carol: I can't say that.
杰克:那么就没人说了.快点.现在说.
Jake: Then nobody can.Come on.Say now.
开萝尔:什么?大声?
Carol: What?Out loud?
杰克:是呀.
Jake: Yeah.
开萝尔:别人会听见的.
Carol: People will hear me.
杰克: 那就对了.喊出来."我 开萝尔 西维尔".
Jake: That's the point.Shout it."I Carol Seaver"
开萝尔:我 开萝尔 西维尔.
Carol: I Carol Seaver.
杰克:再大声点.
Jake: Louder.
开萝尔:我开萝尔 西维尔很漂亮
Carol: I Carol Seaver am beautiful.
杰克:喊出来.
Jake: Shout it.
开萝尔:我很漂亮.
Carol: I'm beautiful.
杰克:还有呢?
Jake: And?
开萝尔:哪个男人不要我,他就是个大傻瓜.
Carol: And any man who doesn't want me is a damn fool.
杰克:喔,呵.对.
Jake: Wooo hooo.Yeah.
开萝尔:哈哈哈.我永远不会忘记今晚.
Carol: Ha ha ha.I am never going to forget this night.
杰克:我也不会,亲爱的.我也不会.
Jake: Neither am I darlin.Neither am I.
麦琪:开萝尔,亲爱的,你还好吧?
Maggie: Carol!Honey, are you alright?
开萝尔:我很漂亮!
Carol: I'm beautiful.
杰森:你发生什么事情了?
Jason: What the heck happened to you?
麦琪:而且为什么你穿的像个流浪的人?
Maggie: And why are you dressed like a gipsy?
开萝尔:我漂亮,不是吗?
Carol: I am aren't I?
杰森:我想知道今晚到底发生了什么事?
Jason: I want to know what's been going on tonight.
开萝尔:魔术.
Carol: Magic.
杰森:魔术.
Jason: Magic!
开萝尔:妈妈,难道这里不是个美好的地方吗?
麦琪:好,在你告诉我魔术是什么意思之后我就让你知道.
00:22:12,300
Carol: Mum, isn't this a wonderful place? Maggie: Well, I'll let you know after you tell me what you mean by magic.